# **Walace Silva**

### Web developer and entrepreneur digital

I'm 26 age old, I'm from city São Paulo and I work with web developer since 2009. Currently to be full-stack freelancer, but has worked in several personal and private projects, some them are below!

linkedin.com/in/walacesilva github.com/wchad walacesilva.com.br

From São Paulo, SP - Brazil + 55 (11) 97775-7308 wsilva.emp@gmail.com me@walacesilva.com.br

#### **SIDE PROJECTS**

## O Mundo do Podólogo — Full-Stack Development <a href="https://omundodopodologo.com">https://omundodopodologo.com</a>

Saas built to podiatry.

## Confrontos FC — Full-Stack Development

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.confrontos

Mobile app to management of match between amauter team soccer.

### **Vyafood** — Backend Development

https://www.vya.com.br

Management system to restaurants.

## Rapfit — Android Development

http://rapfit.com.br

Mobile app to delivery food.

## **Braap Go** — Android Development

https://www.braapgo.com.br

Mobile app for marketplace of tour guides, events of offroad.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Freelancer**, Home office — Web developer

SINCE 2016 - PRESENT

Fullstack.

## **SuperAgendador.com**, São Paulo — *Pleno Web developer*

JANUARY 2015 - DECEMBER 2015

During my trajectory on company I was responsible to implement a new product frontend versions, using tools popularly as AngularJs, RequireJs, Jquery, etc...

#### **SKILLS**

#### Web development

Using variety languages.

#### **PHP**

Using Laravel and CodeIgniter

#### **Ruby**

Using Rails and Sinatra

#### **Javascript**

Using NodeJs, React, ReactNative, Angular, jQuery, ES6-7, etc..

#### **SQL e NoSQL**

Using Mysql/MariaDB, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, etc.

#### **DevOps**

Amazon AWS, DigitalOcean.

#### Mobile

Only Android SDK.

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### **Portuguese:**

Native

#### **English:**

I read and write very well.

## **Agencia Neo Prisms**, Piracicaba — *Pleno Web developer*

JANUARY 2013 - DECEMBER 2014

I did participate of projects as: development of web systems, custom websites from clients requirements, system of marketing of network, tools ads to startups.

<u>Tool Stack:</u> NodeJs, PHP Nativo, PHP Framework Phalcon, Perl, Java, JavaScript, Mysql, Postgresql, Cluster SQL, Bash, Linux OpenSuse..

## **Gtecno - Print Outsourcing,** São Paulo — *Junior Developer*

JUNE 2009 - DECEMBER 2012

In search of news experiences, I did exercise:

- Analyse and implementation of GED/ECM, document digitization.
- Development of legacy solutions.
- Development to corporations website.
- Technical support.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Centro Universitário do Senac**, São Paulo — Tecnologia Jogos Digitais

SINCE 2009 - UNTIL 2013

I did participate of programmer marathon SBC at 2012, organized for IBM with focus in solutions on security of information.

http://maratona.ime.usp.br